Crown for Christmas is a romance, tv movie film directed by Alex Zamm.
Allie Foster, a struggling New York artist, reluctantly accepts to act as a
governess to a rebellious Princess Theodora of Winshire.
When Allie forms an unlikely bond with the princess, she attracts the attention of the handsome
King Maximillian, who’s facing an arranged marriage against his heart’s wishes.
As Christmas Eve draws near, Allie finds herself swept up in
romance, royalty and the spirit of the holidays.
Allie Foster, played by Danica McKellar.
Maximillian, played by Rupert Penry-Jones.
Theodora, played by Ellie Botterill.
Fergus, played by Pavel Douglas.
Chancellor Riggs, played by Colin McFarlane.
Miss Wick, played by Amy Marston.
Crown for Christmas  is a 2015 American made-for-television romantic
comedy film starring Danica McKellar and Rupert Penry-Jones.
The film premiered on Hallmark Channel on November 27, 2015, as part of
their Countdown to Christmas seasonal programming block.
The film explores themes of princess, castle, royalty, king, governess.
The tone is emotional.